Guide to the Frank Moore Papers, 1971-2003 MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Notebooks, 153679
  - Loose items from Notebook #57, 1984; 153753 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Notebook #58, 1984; 153752 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Loose items from Notebook #58, 1984; 153751 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197096 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197097 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Notebook #60, 1984-1985; 153750 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Notebook #61, 1984-1985; 153749 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Notebook #62, 1985; 153748 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Loose items from Notebook #62, 1985; 153747 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Notebook #63, 1985; 153746 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Notebook #64, 1986; 153745 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Loose items from Notebook #64, 1986; 153744 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Notebook #65, 1986; 153743 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Loose items from Notebook #65, 1986; 153742 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Notebook #66, 1987; 153741 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042232424
  - Loose items from Notebook #66, 1987; 153740 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Notebook #67, 1988-1989; 153739 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Loose items from Notebook #67, 1988-1989; 153738 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Notebook #68, 1988-1989; 153737 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Loose items from Notebook #68, 1988-1989; 153736 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Notebook #69, 1989; 153735 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Loose items from Notebook #69, 1989; 153734 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Notebook #70, 1989-1990; 153733 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Loose items from Notebook #70, 1989-1990; 153732 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Notebook #71, 1989-1990; 153731 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Loose items from Notebook #71, 1989-1990; 153730 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Notebook #72, 1989-1990; 153729 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Loose items from Notebook #72, 1989-1990; 153728 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197098 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197099 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Notebook #74, 1990-1991; 153727 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Loose items from Notebook #74, 1990-1991; 153726 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Notebook #75, 1990-1992; 153725 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Notebook #76, 1991; 153724 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Loose items from Notebook #76, 1991; 153723 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Notebook #77, 1991-1994; 153722 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Loose items from Notebook #77, 1991-1994; 153721 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Notebook #78, 1991-1992; 153720 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Loose items from Notebook #78, 1991-1992; 153719 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Notebook #79, 1992; 153718 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042232432
  - Loose items from Notebook #79, 1992; 153717 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Notebook #80, 1992-1993; 153716 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Loose items from Notebook #80, 1992-1993; 153715 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197100 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Loose items from Notebook #81, 1992-1995; 153714 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Notebook #82, 1993-1995; 153713 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Loose items from Notebook #82, 1993-1995; 153712 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Notebook #83, 1993-1994; 153711 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Loose items from Notebook #83, 1993-1994; 153710 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Notebook #84, 1995; 153709 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Loose items from Notebook #84, 1995; 153708 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Notebook #85, 1995; 153707 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Notebook #86, 1995-1996; 153706 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Loose items from Notebook #86, 1995-1996; 153705 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Item removed to oversize, 197101 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Notebook #88, 1996-1997; 153704 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Loose items from Notebook #88, 1996-1997; 153703 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Notebook #89, 1997; 153702 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Loose items from Notebook #89, 1997; 153701 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Notebook #90, 1999; 153700 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Loose items from Notebook #90, 1999; 153699 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Notebook #91, 1999; 153698 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Loose items from Notebook #91, 1999; 153697 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Notebook #92, 1999; 153696 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Loose items Notebook #92, 1999; 153695 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Notebook #93, 2001; 153694 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Loose items from Notebook #93, 2001; 153693 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Notebook #94, 2001-2002; 153692 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042232440
  - Loose items from Notebook #94, 2001-2002; 153691 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Notebook #95, 2001-2002; 153690 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Item removed to oversize, undated; 153689 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Notebook #97, 2001; 153688 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Notebook #98, datebook, 1994; 153687 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Loose items from Notebook #98, 1994; 153686 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Notebook #99, datebook, 1995; 153685 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Loose materials from Notebook #99, 1995; 153684 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Notebook #100, datebook, 1996; 153683 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Loose items from Notebook #100, 1996; 153682 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Notebook #101, 1997; 153681 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Loose items from Notebook #101, 1997; 153680 (Box 6, Folder 172)
- Series II: Art Files, 153303
  This series contains materials relating to Frank Moore's professional career. It is divided into four subseries. The first, subseries A, includes reviews and articles about Frank Moore and his work, announcements for shows, and publications containing his artwork. Subseries B contains administrative files, loan agreements, and financial information. Subseries C consists of notes and lists relating to the day-to-day aspects of his art career. Finally, subseries D includes files of materials Frank Moore collected of other artists' work and careers. Subseries A, B and C are arranged chronologically. Subseries D is arranged alphabetically by the artist's last name.
  - Subseries A: Frank Moore Clippings, Exhibition Announcements, Press, 153514
    - Options and Alternatives: Some Directions in Recent Art. Yale University Art Gallery April 4-May 16, 1973, 153678 (Box 6, Folder 173)
    - Item removed to oversize, 197102 (Box 6, Folder 174)
    - Museum of Modern Art, application to Department of Prints and Illustrated Books, 1978-1979; 153677 (Box 6, Folder 175)
    - P.S. 1 Poetry Project, 1979; 153676 (Box 6, Folder 176)
    - Childhood Show, 1980; 153675 (Box 6, Folder 177)
    - Collaborations, Frank Moore and Jim Self, 1980-1991; 153674 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - Drawing Center, 1980; 153673 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - Invitation Cards to Shows, 1980-1990; 153672 (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - Grey Art Gallery Performance, Jim Self and Frank Moore, 1980; 153671 (Box 6, Folder 181)
    - New York-New Wave. PS 1. February, 1980, 153670 (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - Resumes, 1980-1990; 153669 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - Reviews and Articles, ca. 1980; 153668 (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1980; 153667 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - Watercolor Show at P.S. 1 December 1980, 153666 (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - Blacklight Show at Club 57, June 1981; 197103 (Box 6, Folder 186A)
    - Brooke Alexander Show of Frank Moore and George Negroponte, 1981; 153665 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - CABLE, ca. 1981; 153664 (Box 6, Folder 188)
    - John Heys card, 1981; 153663 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - Lower Manhattan Drawing Show, Curated by Keith Haring. Also known as the First Annual Club 57 Group Erotic and Pornographic Art Exhibition. February 1981, 153662 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1981; 153661 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - 3-7-3 at White Columns, 1981; 153660 (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - Broccoli. Produced by Frank Moore, 1982; 153659 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - Cross Currents, 1982; 153658 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - New Drawing in America at The Drawing Center, 1982; 153657 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Beast: Animal Imagery in Recent Painting, 1982; 197104 (Box 6, Folder 195A)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1982; 153656 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - Collaboration, Frank Moore and Jim Self at the Kitchen, 1983; 153655 (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - New Observations/Better Homes and Gardens, 1983-1984; 153654 (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1983; 153653 (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - Christminster, 1984; 153652 (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - Media Alliance, 1984-1990; 153651 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - Percent for Art Program, 1984; 153650 (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - Phillipe Bonnafont Gallery Show, 1984; 153649 (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - Subway of the Damned, 1984-1985; 153648 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - BACA Downtown, 1985; 153647 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1985; 153646 (Box 7, Folder 206)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042232457
    - Camilla, 1986; 153645 (Box 7, Folder 207)
    - Charles Moulton Dance Co. presents Splatter. Costumes by Frank Moore, 1986; 153644 (Box 7, Folder 208)
    - New York Art Review, 1986; 153643 (Box 7, Folder 209)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1986-1987; 153642 (Box 7, Folder 210)
    - Pentacle, 1986-1988; 153641 (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1986; 153640 (Box 7, Folder 212)
    - Yale Show, 1986; 153639 (Box 7, Folder 213)
    - Materials for the Arts at P.S. 1, 1987; 153638 (Box 7, Folder 214)
    - Palais Bimbo, 1987; 153637 (Box 7, Folder 215)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1987; 153636 (Box 7, Folder 216)
    - American Film Institute Independent Filmmaker Program, 1988; 153635 (Box 7, Folder 217)
    - Crankhouse by Frank Moore and Jim Self, 1988; 153634 (Box 7, Folder 218)
    - Paula Allen Gallery, 1988; 153633 (Box 7, Folder 219)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1988; 153632 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - Empire State Crafts Alliance, 1989-1990; 153631 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - Hargrove Entertainment, 1989; 153630 (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1989; 153629 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - American Dance Asylum M/W/F Video Club, 1990-1992; 153628 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - Art as Object/Object as Art, 1990; 153627 (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - The Bessies, 7th Annual New York Dance and Performance Awards. September 12, 1990, 153626 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - A Day Without Art, 1990; 153625 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - Lincoln Center Exhibit, 1990; 153624 (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - Offstage Attitudes: The Visual Art of Today's Performance Artists. Curated by Frank Moore. July 13-August 2, 1990, 153623 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1990; 153622 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Reviews and Articles, Duplicates, 1990-1991; 153621 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Red Ribbon Slides, Undated; 196863 (Box 7, Folder 231A)
    - "Cruel Things to Do..." by David Cale Charles Moulton and Frank Moore, 1991; 153620 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Invitations and Announcements, 1991-2002; 153619 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Item removed to oversize, 1991; 198459 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1991; 153618 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - Queens Museum, AIDS Panel, 1991; 153617 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - Portrait Show at PS122, 1991; 153616 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1991; 153615 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - Biltekoff, Charlotte. Term paper "Frank Moore: Inspiration in Art and Life", 1992; 153614 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198460 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198461 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - From Media to Metaphor: Art about AIDS, 1992-1994; 153613 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Private/Public at the School of the Art Institute of Chicago., 1992; 153612 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1992; 153611 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Reviews and Articles, Duplicates, 1992-1993; 153610 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - S.A.F.E Portfolio (Special Arts Fund for Emergencies), 1992; 153609 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198462
    - School of Visual Arts, 1992; 153608 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Biography/Selected Bibliography, 1993; 153607 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - The Figure as Fiction, 1993-1994; 153606 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198463 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1993; 153605 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes. "Frank Moore at Sperone Westwater" essay for course at Pratt., 1993; 153604 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Sotheby's Benefit Auction for God's Love We Deliver, June 22, 1993. Includes Frank Moore's painting "Beach Ball", 153603 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Warner, Michael, editor. Fear of a Queer Planet: Queer Politics and Social Theory Frank Moore cover art, 1993; 153602 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Yale Collects Yale April 30-July 31, 1993, 153601 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - AIDS Cure Project Art Show, 1994; 198619 (Box 8, Folder 258)
    - Arabesque, February 18-March 19, 1994 at PPOW, 153600 (Box 8, Folder 259)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042232465
    - Art in America, March 1994, 153599 (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - Art in America, June 1994, 153598 (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - The Blind Man #3, October 1994, 153597 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198620 (Box 8, Folder 263)
    - Lennon, Weinberg Inc. present It's All About Love, an exhibition in commemoration of the Stonewall Riots. June 17-July 29, 1994, 153596 (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1994; 153595 (Box 8, Folder 265)
    - Reviews and Articles, Duplicates, 1994; 153594 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - The Sciences, May/June 1994. Features Frank Moore's paintings in conjunction with article "Whither Doctors? Whence New Drugs?", 153593 (Box 8, Folder 267)
    - Interview, 1995.; 153592 (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - Newsweek, January 9, 1995. Frank Moore included in "New Faces for the New Year", 153591 (Box 8, Folder 269)
    - Requested documentation, compiled ca. 1995, 153590 (Box 8, Folder 270)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1995; 153589 (Box 8, Folder 271)
    - Reviews and Articles, Duplicates, 1995-1998; 153588 (Box 8, Folder 272)
    - Sperone Westwater Show, March 25-April 22, 1995, 153587 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198621 (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - Art at the End of the 20th Century, 1996; 153586 (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - Art's AIDS Communities: Realizing the Archive Project, 1996; 153585 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - Changing Horizons: Landscape on the Eve of the Millenium., 1996; 153584 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - Estate Planning for Artists, Fall 1996, 153583 (Box 8, Folder 278)
    - Frank Moore at Gian Enzo Sperone, January 1996, Rome, 153582 (Box 8, Folder 279)
    - Give Life to Art: The First Step presented by Gallery Positive and Visual AIDS, 153581 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    - Go Magazine, 1996; 153580 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Invitation: American Art of Today from the Misumi Collection, 1996; 153579 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198622 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    - Miller, Mara Jayne. MA Thesis, Bard College. "Nature/Culture and the Postmodern Sublime: Frank Moore and Gregory Crewdson", 1996; 153578 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - POZ: Hope, Health and HIV, 1996; 153577 (Box 8, Folder 285)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1996; 153576 (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - Statements about his won work, ca. 1996; 153575 (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - Whitney Catalogue, 1996; 153574 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Discover: The World of Science. June 1997. Frank Moore Paintings accompany "Immune to a Plague", 153573 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - Gianni Versace. Memorial at the Metropolitan in New York, November 8, 1997, 153572 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198623 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198624 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - Poliester vol. 6 no. 20 Fall 1997, 153571 (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1997; 153570 (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Versace, Gianni. The Art of Being You., 1997; 153569 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198625 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Estate Planning for Artists, 1998; 153568 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Frank Moore March 28-April 25, 1998 at Sperone Westwater, 153567 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Pollution, 1998; 153566 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1998; 153565 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Sea Change. The Parrish Art Museum, Southampton New York, 1998; 153564 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Skowhegan Fall 1998 Newsletter, 153563 (Box 9, Folder 302)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042232473
    - "Zulu Love Letter AIDS Ribbon", ca. 1998; 153562 (Box 9, Folder 303)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters Award [materials also located in oversize box], 1999; 153561 (Box 9, Folder 304)
    - Bodies of Resistance. Curated by Barbara Hunt. shown at Real Art Ways, Hartford CT, November 21-December 31, 1999 and KNSA Gallery, Durban South Africa: July 2000., 1999-2000; 153560 (Box 9, Folder 305)
    - The Choice, 1999; 153559 (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1999; 153558 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    - Art on Paper 2000, Weatherspoon Art Gallery, 153557 (Box 9, Folder 308)
    - Arte Americana: Ultimo Decennio, 2000; 153556 (Box 9, Folder 309)
    - Paradise Now, 2000; 153555 (Box 9, Folder 310)
    - Paradise Now Photographs, 2000; 153554 (Box 9, Folder 311)
    - Reviews and Articles, 2000; 153553 (Box 9, Folder 312)
    - Sperone, Gian Enzo Torino Roma New York 1972-1999., 2000; 153552 (Box 9, Folder 313)
    - da Warhol al 2000, 153551 (Box 9, Folder 314)
    - Announcement. Inaugural Art Exhibit, curated by Jim Pavlicovic. August 17-September 29, 2001, 153550 (Box 9, Folder 315)
    - Episala, Joy. The Physical Photograph. Essay by Frank Moore, 2001; 153549 (Box 9, Folder 316)
    - Green on Greene. Sperone Westwater, 2001; 153548 (Box 9, Folder 317)
    - Home Style. October 2001, 153547 (Box 9, Folder 318)
    - Paradise Now at the Tang Teaching Museum. Skidmore College, 2001; 153546 (Box 9, Folder 319)
    - POZ, January 2001, 153545 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Reviews and Articles, 2001; 153544 (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - The Sciences. January/February 2001, 153543 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Speeches about work: Paradise Now, 2001-2002; 153542 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - Visual AIDS, 2001; 153541 (Box 9, Folder 324)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198626 (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - Frank Moore: Green Thumb in a Dark Eden. Orlando Museum of Art, June 8-July 28, 2002, 153540 (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198627 (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - New York Philharmonic Concert in the Parks. Designed by Harvey Weiss and dedicated to Frank Moore., 2002; 153539 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198628 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198629 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198630 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Reviews and Articles, 2002; 153538 (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Tribute to Frank Moore, June 19, 2002. Guestbook, 153537 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - Update: New York Academy of Sciences Magazine, 2002; 153536 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - Bookplate, 2003; 153535 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Members Preview Invitation to Green Thumb in a Dark Eden. Buffalo Fine Arts Academy. January 31, 2003, 153534 (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - AIDS Red-ribbon sticker from France, undated; 153533 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Artists Space, undated; 153532 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Bee Stationary, undated; 153531 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Book Plate, undated; 153530 (Box 9, Folder 340)
    - Miscellaneous Booklet, undated; 153529 (Box 9, Folder 341)
    - Cards/Postcards of Frank Moore's Artwork, undated; 153528 (Box 9, Folder 342)
    - Miscellaneous Dance, undated; 153527 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Fallen Idylls, American Figurative Painting, undated; 153526 (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198631 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Gesso Foundation. 501(c)(3). Established by Frank Moore to "place his art for maximum public benefit.", undated; 153525 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Gulliver painting on small square card, undated; 153524 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Invitation for Tim Dlugos, Richard Elovich and Brad Gooch reading, design by Frank Moore, undated; 153523 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - Moore, Christine. Report on Frank Moore by his niece., undated; 153522 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - "Out of the Blue" flier, undated; 153521 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Private Mythologies, undated; 153520 (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198632 (Box 9, Folder 352)
    - Sundance Institute, undated; 153519 (Box 9, Folder 353)
    - Toast to Frank Moore. [by Nick?], undated; 153518 (Box 9, Folder 354)
    - Visual AIDS, undated; 153517 (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - Visual AIDS Competition, undated; 153516 (Box 9, Folder 356)
    - Item removed to oversize, 153515 (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Subseries B: Frank Moore Administrative, 153491
    - Crosby Street Housing, Artist Cooperative, 1980-1988; 153513 (Box 9, Folder 358)
    - NEA Grant Material, 1981; 153512 (Box 9, Folder 359)
    - Credit Cards, 1983; 153511 (Box 9, Folder 360)
    - Pentacle, 1986; 153510 (Box 9, Folder 361)
    - Primary Performance Group, 1987; 153509 (Box 9, Folder 362)
    - New York Foundation of the Arts:Artists' Fellowship Award, 1988; 153508 (Box 9, Folder 363)
    - Paula Allen Gallery, 1988-1989; 153507 (Box 9, Folder 364)
    - Receipts, 1988-1990; 153506 (Box 9, Folder 365)
    - Rothko conservation, 1989; 153505 (Box 9, Folder 366)
    - Joffrey Ballet, 1990-1991; 153504 (Box 9, Folder 367)
    - Mid-Atlantic Arts Foundation Grant/NEA, 1990; 153503 (Box 9, Folder 368)
    - Paula Allen Gallery Pricelist, 1990; 153502 (Box 9, Folder 369)
    - Queens Museum AIDS Panel, 1991; 153501 (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - Restoration estimate, icicle frame on Hospital, 1994; 153500 (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - The Baer Faxt- Recent Sales, 1995; 153499 (Box 10, Folder 372)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042232481
    - Great Lakes United, 1997; 153498 (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - Primary Performance Group, Annual Report, 1998; 153497 (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Hopefulmonster Editore: Book Project request, 2000; 153496 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Addresses, undated; 153495 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Addresses, undated; 153494 (Box 10, Folder 377)
    - To Do Lists, undated; 153493 (Box 10, Folder 378)
    - Wessel O'Connor Gallery, Loan contract. [found inside menu, Chanterelle, dated January 22-February 17, 1996], undated; 153492 (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Subseries C: Frank Moore Miscellaneous Fragments, 153453
    - Materials taken from ABC de la Peinture, undated; 153490 (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - Materials taken from Alexander Pushkin: Complete Prose Fiction, undated; 153489 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Materials taken from The Ancient Roman Villa of Casale, undated; 153488 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - Materials taken from Animus and Anima, undated; 153487 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Item removed to oversize, 198694 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - Materials taken from Art in America, 1994; 153486 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Materials taken from Christianity, Social Tolerance and Homosexuality, undated; 153485 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Materials taken from Chronicle: The Human Side of AIDS, undated; 153484 (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Materials taken from Creative Evolution, undated; 153483 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - Materials taken from Cunault, 1979; 153482 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Materials taken from The Dead Lecturer by LeRoi Jones, undated; 153481 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Inscription from Diego Rivera, undated; 153480 (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Materials taken from Les Fleurs du Mae, undated; 153479 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Materials taken from Henry Moore: Unpublished Drawings, undated; 153478 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    - Materials taken from Herodotus: The Struggle for Greece, undated; 153477 (Box 10, Folder 394)
    - Materials taken from A History of Costume, 1994; 153476 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - Materials taken from Hommage a Derain, undated; 153475 (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - Materials taken from The Life of Sharks, undated; 153474 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - Materials taken from Living Insects of the World, undated; 153473 (Box 10, Folder 398)
    - Materials taken from Marcel Duchamp, undated; 153472 (Box 10, Folder 399)